CONTACT INFO

Phone

203-644-9813

Email

perrinbrown@optonline.net

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/perrin-brown

Website

perrinbrown.com

Github

github.com/perrinbrown129

Location

Greater NYC Area, willing to relocate

SKILLS

Languages

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, MongoDB

Software

WordPress, Photoshop,
Google Analytics & Adwords,
Zoho, Unleashed,
Dropbox, Smartsheet,
Stitchlabs, Klaviyo, Metrilo,
Constant Contact,
Mailchimp, Microsoft Office,
Canva

Social Media

Facebook, Twitter, Tumblr, Instagram, Pinterest

INTERESTS

LGBTQ+ advocacy, gluten-free food, ice hockey, field hockey & puzzles

Perrin Brown

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

Dependable and proactive software engineer with a background in e-commerce and social media, passionate about building and supporting teams. A creative problem solver with skills in research and analysis who can effectively and succinctly organize data. Aims to work at a user-focused and inclusive company making an impact on the world.

EXPERIENCE

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Engineering Fellow | September 2019 - December 2019

- Completed full-stack web development at General Assembly's immersive program and expanded technical toolkit by learning HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, RESTful APIs, jQuery, Node.js, React.js, SQL, GitHub and Heroku to build a portfolio of web apps including a directory for gluten-free beverages, a television show recommendation site and a database for LGBTQ+ owned online e-commerce businesses

BULLDOG YOGA

E-Commerce Business Development Associate | August 2017 - August 2019

- Increased social media engagement & sales by partnering with 100+ influencers, podcasts, blogs, businesses & subscription boxes
- Engaged with customers for technical support at all times, designed marketing emails and coordinated press releases

BODHI TREE LLC

Editorial Assistant | April 2016 - June 2017

- Helped launch a metaphysical book store's website while managing "Journal" writers and researching article ideas
- Worked in WordPress CMS to configure landing pages, upload articles, enhance UX and SEO

NAPA VALLEY FILM FESTIVAL

Hospitality Assistant | August 2015 - January 2016

- Organized local housing for over 100 filmmakers & industry representatives associated with 50+ films
- Designed itineraries & welcome packages for filmmakers, while communicating with their representatives

EDUCATION

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Certificate of Completion, Software Engineering Immersive | December 2019

VENTURE FOR AMERICA

Fellow, VFA WMN Leader & Entrepreneur | August 2017

DARTMOUTH COLLEGE

B.A. Asian & Middle Eastern Studies | June 2015